(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Agent V7, are you there yet?
Yes, we'll be landing in a bit.
Okay, listen up. This time your mission is to steal a key.
Ya, ya, ya. A key.
Hm? A key? What key?
Huh? Jump? What do you mean "jump"?
No... Now?
Hello? Hello?
Okay, I guess I have to jump now.
Here goes nothing.
Three, two, one!
今夜はから騒ぎ
Much Ado About Tonight
みずぎわ わいては満ちて
By the shore, rising and falling like the tide
胸騒ぎ
My heart skips a beat
もう一度潮時よ 顔と名前の貸借
It's high tide once again, borrowing a face and a name
足を洗うべきよ 媚と恨みの売買
I should wash my hands of this, of flattery and selling grudges
目尻の涙は真相は見せないで
Don't let the tears in my eyes reveal the truth
語るまじ 気まぐれ世の煩い
I won't speak of it, the fickle troubles of this world
当然の報いだよ 仇と利息の返済
It's a natural consequence, paying back vengeance and interest
手を染めた罰よ 恩と喧嘩の売買
It's punishment for dirtying my hands, trading favors and fights
裏切りの頂で衝動は問わないで
At the peak of betrayal, don't ask about the impulse
さようなら 恋煩い
Farewell, lovesickness
浮かばれるか沈むか暗愚のTOKYO港湾
To float or to sink, in the foolish Tokyo harbor
ずらからにゃパクられてまう ああ 青息吐息
If I don't flee I'll be caught, ah, gasping for breath
笑顔が眩しいね 見納め小雨
Your smile is so dazzling, a last look at the light rain
...雨
...drizzle
小雨
Drizzle
泡沫を喰っちゃ泡沫を吹かす大博打思惑師
A gambler who eats bubbles and blows bubbles, a schemer
赤プリがもぬけならば名ばかりの紀尾井町
If the Akasaka Prince Hotel is empty, Kioicho is just a name
終わりゆく時代へ投げキス毎度あり型通り
A blowing kiss to the ending era, thank you as always, just as planned
あの八番出口もヨウナシね…溜池山王
That exit number 8 is also useless now... Tameike-Sanno
みずぎわ　引いては満ちて
The water's edge, ebbing and flowing
胸騒ぎ
My heart flutters
みずぎわ　引いては満ちて
The water's edge, ebbing and flowing
泡沫... 胸騒ぎ
Bubbles... My heart flutters
Yay!
Yay! Hello everyone!
Welcome to my 3D Showcase!
But before we get further, if you see here...
Oh! Oops! Here!
Here's the hashtag. If you want to use the hashtag...
silakan pakai hashtag-nya kalau kalian mau nge-tweet
Please use the hashtag if you want to tweet
apapun, share ke siapapun. Yay, yay, yay!
anything, share with anyone. Yay, yay, yay!
Yay! How is it?
こんぜた！から騒ぎ！
Kon-Zeta! Gazawagi!
Oh, there's also Bazo!
If you guys... you guys are always wondering,
where is Bazo 3D? バゾ3Dどこ？
where is Bazo 3D? Where is Bazo 3D?
ここだよ、バゾ3D！
It's here, Bazo 3D!
Yay! かわいいね、バゾ？
Yay! Isn't Bazo cute?
Oh!
Okay, so now, I want to show off...
my body, I guess? My clothes!
Don't you guys want to see?
Kalian mau lihat nggak sih? Dari...
Don't you guys want to see? From...
Hah!
Wheeya! Wheeya!
Hati-hati biar nggak nendang cameraman.
Careful not to kick the cameraman.
Whoo! Maybe I should do a twirl?
Whoo! Tadah!
Yeah! Okay, and then...
My thighs, 太もも！
My thighs, thighs!
Yay! There's like, what is this called?
Thigh-highs? Yeah, thigh-highs.
In the same move.
And then the skirt.
And then the lock.
By the way, speaking of lock...
where's the - where's the key?
Kuncinya ke mana tadi? Hmm...
Where did the key go? Hmm...
I - I guess if you guys don't know, we're on the mission...
What?! La...
Sekretari!
Ah! 鍵持ってるじゃん！
Ah! You have the key!
Sekretari, give me the key! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Give me the key! Sekretari! Hurry!
Kasih kuncinya! Sekretari!
Give me the key! Sekretari!
No! No! No!
Sekretari! Wait! Bazo! Bazo!
Hurry up! Let's go!
Let's take the key!
にゃ？
Nya?
BAZOMINT 200IQ TOOTHPASTE MILK
Yee! We finally arrived!
So where's the key? Where's the key, Bazzo? Tell me where's the key!
Bazzo, can you think of where the key is?
Okay, Bazzo doesn't think.
Bazzo nggak bisa mikir, dia nggak tahu kuncinya di mana.
Bazzo can't think, he doesn't know where the key is.
Okay... uhm...
Ini pintu... lah!
This door... wait!
Bentar bentar bentar, ini laser nggak sih?
Wait, wait, wait, are these lasers?
Kocak sih kocak kebangetan, laser woy!
This is hilarious, it's so funny, lasers, guys!
That's crazy! What the heck?
Why would a laser be here?
Okay, you know what? I get it. It's like security and all that.
Okay, security, it's okay, I've been through this.
I'm the master of infiltration!
I'm literally the best secret agent in the world. I can do this.
Bazzo, can you do it?
Heh, Bazzo... Bazzo's... you know, Bazzo probably can do it.
I'll show you how to do it.
You know what, but I don't know if the key is even...
Ah...
おい。え？
Hey. Huh?
Sekretaris? Itu sekretaris?
Secretary? Is that the secretary?
Itu sekretaris? Itu sekretaris kah?
Is that the secretary? Is that the secretary?
Oh iya, itu sekretaris!
Oh yeah, that's the secretary!
あ！ Sekretaris！ Ke mana？！
Ah! Secretary! Where are you going?!
Wah, malah kabur dong!
Wow, he's actually running away!
Tunggu bentar, kabur!
Wait a minute, he's running away!
Gimana? Terus gimana?
How? Then what?
Terus gimana kalau dia kabur?
Then what if he runs away?
Terus gimana kalau misalnya dia kabur?
Then what if, for example, he runs away?
Bazzo, kamu nggak mau duluan?
Bazzo, don't you want to go first?
Bazzo, kejar! Bazzo kejar!
Bazzo, chase him! Bazzo, chase him!
Go! Go! Chase after him!
Chase after him! You can do it!
Hey, isn't that cheating? He's just like going straight.
That's cheating! Hey, yeah, that's cheating!
ズルいそれ！
That's cheating!
That's cheating, he just went straight. Now what?
Now what? Now I'm left alone.
Okay, it's okay. I can do this.
For the sake of my mission, I shall show to you...
...what a secret agent is truly like.
Okay... uhm... uhm... ah...
Merangkak dulu nggak sih?
Should I crawl first?
Maybe if I crawl under here...
...maybe... maybe it'll work if I crawl under.
Wah! Aduh, duh, duh, duh, duh...
Waah! Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Nggak sakit sih, tapi bohong nggak sakit.
It doesn't hurt, but just kidding, it does hurt.
It doesn't hurt, but... uhm...
Okay, that's because of my hair buns, my ears, or whatever you call it.
Okay, what about... what if I step over?
If I step over, maybe... Huaa!
Wah! Aduh, duh, duh, duh!
Wah! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Sakit dah. That hurts.
It hurts. That hurts.
Okay... Nggak tahu! Aku udah kehabisan ide, capek.
Okay... I don't know! I'm out of ideas, tired.
Capek aku. Kalian komen apa kek, kasih ide.
I'm tired. You guys comment something, give me ideas.
Kasih ide. Give me ideas on how I should cross this one then.
Give me ideas. Give me ideas on how I should cross this one then.
Ah, you guys can comment. But, oh, you know what? I just thought of something.
Kenapa nggak ini aja?
Why not just this?
Ini aja nggak sih guys?
Just this, right guys?
Kayang aja nggak sih guys?
How about doing a bridge pose, guys?
Kayang aja nggak sih?
How about doing a bridge pose?
Kayang! Ready? Tiga, dua, satu!
Bridge! Ready? Three, two, one!
Ah! Nggak bisa!
Ah! I can't!
Wah! Ini bisa sih.
Wah! This might work.
Ini kayaknya bisa deh.
I think this might work.
If I do bridge like this, I can cross... ah, adeh.
If I do bridge like this, I can cross... ah, oh no.
Is it just me or did the laser just go up?
Somebody's operating it. Okay, well... okay, this is easy.
Limbo! We just have to do limbo, right?
Uh... Limbo! Ah! Aduh!
Uh... Limbo! Ah! Ouch!
Okay, okay, what do I do?
Aduuh! Wah, nggak bisa juga.
Ouch! Wow, that doesn't work either.
Okay, okay, nggak bisa, nggak bisa. Yo...
Okay, okay, it doesn't work, it doesn't work. Yo...
Ah...
You just have to crawl.
Look at that, that was stupid. That was stupid.
Because I said that, then that never happened.
Adah...
Ouch...
Okay, okay... ah... ah...
Just keep crawling I guess.
If I keep crawling, maybe I'll reach the destination faster.
Ah... what about this one?
What about... ah...
Aduh, ini tuh nggak bisa tembus tembok aja ya?
Ouch, can't I just phase through the wall?
Capek, serius.
I'm tired, seriously.
Aduh, kena! Kena! Rambutku kena!
Ouch, I got hit! I got hit! My hair got hit!
Okay... okay... watch me crawl again.
Watch this, watch this, watch this, chat, watch, watch.
Ah! Let's go! Ah... ah...
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Ah!
Yeah. Sorry.
oshiri too big.
My butt is too big.
Okay, yay!
Weehee! Yatta!
Weehee! We did it!
That was so easy.
That was so easy. See?
I'm literally the best agent out there.
Literally the best agent out there.
Easy, gampang itu mah.
Easy, that's easy.
Gampang!
Easy!
Ini apaan?
What is this?
Ini curang nggak sih?
Isn't this cheating?
Ini tuh kayak apa sih, kayak main game
It's like, you know, playing a game
terus level boss-nya tiba-tiba muncul di akhir.
and then the boss level suddenly appears at the end.
Kesel.
So annoying.
Okay, whatever.
There's like a new... what?
Ah! And it's moving.
This is so unfair.
これずるいな...
This is unfair...
いけるかな?
Can I do it?
I don't know if I can make it.
Okay. Um...
put your bets if I can... if you guys think I can make it.
Three, two, wah tapi bohong.
Three, two, wah just kidding.
Three, two, one! Woah!
Yeah, yatta! Let's go! Let's go, we made it!
Yeah, we did it! Let's go! Let's go, we made it!
Bazo? Bazo-re? Bazo...
Bazo... Bazo-nya kabur duluan.
Bazo... Bazo ran away first.
Bazo nggak ada. Ya udahlah.
Bazo is gone. Oh well.
Ya udah, ayo sekarang kita kejar Sekretari.
Alright, let's go catch Secretary now.
Ayo cepat, cepat-cepat-cepat.
Come on, hurry, hurry-hurry-hurry.
Ayo! Lekas! Lekas! Lekas!
Come on! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Mana key? I've got to find the key.
Where's the key? I've got to find the key.
Wah, wah! Hah?
Ini ruangan apaan?
What kind of room is this?
Aneh banget sumpah. Eh?
It's so weird, I swear. Eh?
This is such a weird room.
Where's the key? Ah! Ah! Ah!
There's Bazo and Secretary!
Eh? The key! 鍵持ってる!
Eh? The key! They have the key!
Bazo, 頂だい!
Bazo, give it to me!
Eh? Eh? Eh? 飛ぶん! Wah!
Eh? Eh? Eh? I'm flying! Wah!
Gimana? Ke dalam? Ah!
How? Inside? Ah!
鍵が... 中にいる? もしかして。
Is the key... inside? Maybe.
あれ? Eh? Ah, ah, ah.
Huh? Eh? Ah, ah, ah.
Sekretari! Ah! 教えて、教えて!
Secretary! Ah! Tell me, tell me!
Ini gimana, ini gimana, harus ngapain aku?
How does this work? What should I do?
Ah... I see, I see. Okay, okay.
So somebody has to press the button, right?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, somebody has to press the button
so I can get the key. Okay, okay.
Okay, わかった。 I get it now.
Okay, I understand. I get it now.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
え... 誰かいないかな?
Eh... is anyone there?
誰か助けて!
Someone help me!
助けて! そう言ったの...
Help me! Did someone say that...
誰か助けて!
Someone help me!
今助けてって言ったの誰誰誰誰誰...
Who just said "help me"? Who who who who who...
Zeta! あ! 誰かが来た!
Zeta! Ah! Someone came!
あ! 尾丸ポルカ様! Yay!
Ah! Omaru Polka-sama! Yay!
どうした Zeta? どうしたの?
What's wrong Zeta? What happened?
どうしたの? どうしたの?
What happened? What happened?
え? ここどこ? どうしたの?
Eh? Where are we? What happened?
あ! Big! どうしたの?
Ah! Big! What happened?
えーと、鍵。鍵を中にいる。
Um, the key. The key is inside.
はい。えー... じゃあ、ここ、ロック、バン!
Yes. Eh... then, here, lock, bang!
っていうことで。
That's how we'll do it.
だめ、だめだめだめ!
No, no-no-no-no!
なんで? 壊しちゃだめ!
Why? Don't break it!
Don't, don't, don't destroy it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Why? Why? Why? Why not?
Why? Why? Why? Why?
おかしいな。ポルカ先輩...
That's strange. Polka-senpai...
ボタンを... 押してください。
Please... press the button.
じゃあ、二人で一緒に協力して。
Then, let's cooperate together.
こうやって... えーと、あれの中に Zeta がこうやって
Like this... um, Zeta will go inside there like this
「ウィーン、ウィーン」って、先の... そうそうそう。
and go "ween, ween", like before... right, right, right.
鍵を「ウィーン、ウィーン」って取ってくるから。
You'll go "ween, ween" and grab the key.
じゃあ、ポルカがここでボタン押すから。
Then Polka will press the button here.
はい、はい、はい。
Yes, yes, yes.
じゃあ、 Zeta はもうそこで「ウィーン」ってされておいで。
Then Zeta, go and get "ween"-ed over there.
頑張るから。任せる。
I'll do my best. I'll leave it to you.
任せる。頑張る。任せる。
I'll leave it to you. Do your best. I'll leave it to you.
Secretary is useless though.
Okay, 任せる。
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがとう。
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
じゃあ、行ってらっしゃい。ありがとう。
Well then, have a safe trip. Thank you.
うん、帰ってきてね、必ず。
Yeah, come back for sure.
うん。本当に帰ってくるかな?
Yeah. Will she really come back?
大丈夫かな?
Will she be okay?
あ! あ! Zeta ちゃん!
Ah! Ah! Zeta-chan!
Zeta!
そんなことになっちゃってるけど大丈夫?
You've ended up like that, are you okay?
Zeta? Zeta?
ポルカ先輩! 助けて!
Polka-senpai! Help me!
助けてじゃないよ。
It's not "help me".
Zeta を助けに行くんでしょう?
We're going to save Zeta, right?
Zeta も助け、 Bazo も助けないといけないのかポルカは。
Polka has to save Zeta and Bazo?
助けて!
Help me!
鍵探しに行くぞ!
Let's go find the key!
うん、うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
じゃあポルカがこのボタン乗るから。
Then Polka will get on this button.
教えてどの辺か。
Tell me where it is.
Okay, okay, okay. お願い。
Okay, okay, okay. Please.
あー、大変そうだな。
Ah, looks like it'll be tough.
行くよ! じゃあ右から、せーの...
Here I go! Okay, from the right, one-two...
やー! やー! やー! 右だ!
Yaa! Yaa! Yaa! It's the right!
わ、わ、大変。わ、わ...
Whoa, whoa, this is tough. Whoa, whoa...
高いの平気? ちなみに。
Are you okay with heights? By the way.
高いの怖くない?
Aren't you afraid of heights?
いや、怖くない。全然怖くない。
No, I'm not. I'm not afraid at all.
あ、じゃあここだ! はい、下! やー!
Ah, then it's here! Okay, down! Yaa!
行く！行く！
Go! Go!
離れる。
Leaving.
左、左。To the left.
Left, left. To the left.
無理です。動かせないです、こんなに。そんなに器用に動かないです。
It's impossible. I can't move like this. I can't move that skillfully.
どこがどこ辺そう？どこら辺そう？
Where, about where? About where is it?
見えた？
See it?
うん、うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
あ、見えた！
Ah, I see it!
これわ…？
Is this...?
これ鍵持ってないかな…？
Does this one not have the key...?
鍵どこ？
Where's the key?
There's no key!
それね、多分ハズレだ。
That's probably a miss.
ハズレ！？
A miss!?
それは多分普通のバゾだわ。
That's probably just a normal Bazo.
そうです。そうです。
That's right. That's right.
でも普通のバゾも可愛いからね。こっちね。
But the normal Bazo is cute too, right here.
あ、そんなに雑に投げられて…可哀想に。
Ah, being thrown so roughly... poor thing.
もう一回行こう。
Let's go again.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
大丈夫？そろそろ、あのなんか底ってさ、どんな感じ？
Are you okay? By now, how does the bottom feel down there?
高い？怖い？
Is it high? Is it scary?
ううん、怖くない、怖くない。
No, it's not scary, not scary.
怖くないね！
Not scary!
じゃあ早めに行った方がいい。怖くない！
Then we should go quickly. Not scary!
じゃあもう一回さね。行くよ。
Then one more time. Here we go.
あ、ノー！はい！はい！
Ah, no! Yes! Yes!
うわあ！どうする？どこだ？
Whoa! What should we do? Where is it?
ポルカ先輩、あと何秒？
Polka-senpai, how many seconds left?
三…どこら辺？あ、見えた、見えた？
Three... about where? Ah, did you see it? See it?
見えた！
I see it!
見えた、見えた、見えた！
I see it, see it, see it!
行くよ、はい、ストップ！
Going, hey, stop!
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
どこだ？これはさすがに行ったんじゃない？
Where? Didn't we get it this time?
ここじゃないかも…
It might not be here...
嘘でしょ！？
No way!?
ここじゃないかも。ね、ポルカ先輩、ここじゃないかも。
It might not be here. Hey, Polka-senpai, it might not be here.
いや、まだわかんない。見えない…うん。
No, we don't know yet. Can't see... yeah.
え！？あー！
Eh!? Aaa!
なんで！？
Why!?
まずい！？やばいって、それは！それよ！
Bad!? That's bad! That's it!
爆発？焦げた？
Explosion? Did it burn?
あれ？大丈夫？
Huh? Are you okay?
あれ？大丈夫じゃないかも。
Huh? Maybe I'm not okay.
線切れてない？大丈夫？
Is the line cut? Are you okay?
まあ、そういう時のためにね、ホロライブはね、いつもこうやって頑張ってますから。大丈夫ですよ。
Well, for times like this, Hololive is always working hard like this. It's okay.
ゼータさんはこうやって無事です。
Zeta-san is safe like this.
いや、私無事じゃないよ。
No, I'm not safe.
え！無事じゃないの！？
Eh! You're not safe!?
無事じゃないよ！
I'm not safe!
じゃあなんとかして早く！無事を確かめなくちゃ。
Then do something quickly! We have to confirm you're safe.
待って、でもよかった、黒焦げだけで済んで。よかった、よかった。じゃあ行くよ、ゼータ。
Wait, but I'm glad it only ended with you being charred black. Good, good. Okay, let's go, Zeta.
Okay、もうちょっとだよ。頑張ろう、ゼータ。
Okay, just a bit more. Let's do our best, Zeta.
ゼータ、本気で探して。
Zeta, look for it for real.
Okay, okay.
みんなも「頑張って」って、「ゼータ頑張れ」ってコメントして！
Everyone too, say "do your best". Comment "Zeta do your best"!
Okay, okay, okay.
そういうこと。Cheer for me.
That's right. Cheer for me.
Okay, cheer for me, okay. じゃあ行くぞ。せーの、おらあ！
Okay, cheer for me, okay. Here we go. Ready, ora!
おお！おお！最後か？あ、あ、ちょっと！
Oh! Oh! Is it the last one? Ah, ah, wait!
ゼータ、ちょっと、ちょっと右かも。ちょっと右かも。
Zeta, wait, maybe a little to the right. Maybe a little to the right.
Just stop! Hey!
いや、ああ！Okay, okay, okay.
No, aa! Okay, okay, okay.
ゼータが頑張ってこうやって「ふう、ふう」ってやってる。
Zeta is doing her best like "phew, phew".
見える、見える？見えてきた？
Can you see, see? Is it coming into view?
うん、うん、見える。
Yeah, yeah, I see it.
見える、見える、見える。
I see it, see it, see it.
これじゃない？
Isn't it this one?
ああ！それですゼータ！それ！正解、正解、正解のバゾです、それは！
Aa! That's it Zeta! That! Correct, correct, that's the correct Bazo!
おお！いい眺めだなぁ、上から見て。
Oh! It's a nice view looking from above.
これ合ってるかな？
Is this correct?
それ合ってますよ、ゼータさん。それ合ってます。
That's correct, Zeta-san. That's correct.
おめでとう！やったー！
Congratulations! We did it!
ああ、落ちてきた。ありがとう！
Aa, it fell down. Thank you!
これ鍵だ。ゼータ、早く降りてこないと、ゼータが今度大変なことになっちゃうから。
This is the key. Zeta, if you don't come down quickly, something bad will happen to Zeta next.
下ろしてあげなきゃ。下ろすぞ。今待ってろ、ゼータ。
I have to let you down. I'm letting you down. Wait for it, Zeta.
ゼーター！
Zetaaa!
うわ！ゼータ！出てくる、出てくる。見てて、見てて。
Whoa! Zeta! She's coming out, coming out. Watch, watch.
ああ、ほら！ゼータ！可愛い！
Aa, look! Zeta! Cute!
出た！おめでとう！感動の再会。あ、ぎゅうしてあげてよ。
She's out! Congratulations! An emotional reunion. Ah, give her a hug.
あ、はいはい。ぎゅうね。はい。
Ah, okay, okay. A hug. Yes.
シニを。え？シニ？
To Sini. Eh? Sini?
まあ、シニ、賢いじゃん。
Well, Sini, you're smart, aren't you?
Sini, give me the key. Give me the key.
早く、give me the key.
Hurry, give me the key.
ポコポコ。
Poko-poko.
鍵ちょうだい。
Give me the key.
ははは。ポコポコ殴ってたよ、今。
Hahaha. You were hitting it poko-poko just now.
あ、鍵もらえた？大丈夫？
Ah, did you get the key? Are you okay?
もらった！
I got it!
あ、よかった。もらった。じゃあね。
Ah, good. You got it. Bye then.
え！？じゃあね？
Eh!? Bye then?
鍵もらったよ。
I got the key.
おめでとう。でもいいの？なんか殴られてたけど。
Congratulations. But is it okay? You were being hit though.
いやいや、大丈夫。大丈夫。
No no, it's okay. It's okay.
あれが、あれがいいんだ。
That, that's what's good.
あれが求められてるものらしいですね、みなさん。
It seems like that's what's being sought after, everyone.
よかった、おめでとう。
I'm glad, congratulations.
ありがとう！頑張った甲斐があった。
Thank you! It was worth the effort.
鍵もらったぞ！
I got the key!
いぇーい！
Yeeey!
じゃあ、もしかしてポルカ先輩、頑張ったからさ、なんか、くれないかな？
So, maybe since Polka-senpai worked hard, could I get something?
ええ！？「え」って何？「え」って何？
Ehh!? What's with the "eh"? What's with the "eh"?
うーん、じゃあ…
Umm, then...
これ、あげるかな。
I'll give you this.
くれる？何くれる？
You'll give me? What will you give me?
はい。え？あ、あ、足っぽ可愛い。足っぽ可愛い。
Yes. Eh? Ah, ah, the tail is cute. The tail is cute.
え、急に何？
Eh, what all of a sudden?
Okay, tada!
うわ、何これ？何これ？
Whoa, what's this? What's this?
ゼタミン！
Zetamin!
ゼタミン！？
Zetamin!?
ゼタミン！
Zetamin!
ほー！
Ho!
これは飲むとどうなる？
What happens if I drink this?
これ飲んだら、if you drink this, 200 IQ. 200 IQ.
If you drink this, 200 IQ. 200 IQ.
あー！200 IQ！IQ 200！
Aa! 200 IQ! IQ 200!
うん、IQ 200。ゼータのようになれちゃう。
Yeah, IQ 200. You'll become just like Zeta.
ゼータ…ゼータ…
Zeta... Zeta...
これでゲットできた。
I got it with this.
鍵もゲットしたもんね。
We got the key too, right?
うん。
Yeah.
これでじゃあ、ゼータはもう次の部屋に行けるってこと。
With this, Zeta can go to the next room.
うん。
Yeah.
そうだね。
That's right.
ああ、良かった！おめでとう！
Ah, great! Congratulations!
あ、ちょっと待って。これ置くから。ちょっと二人で写真、写真。
Ah, wait a second. I'll put this down.
Let's take a photo, the two of us.
あ、はい、はい。
Ah, yes, yes.
えー、ピース、ピース。イエーイ。
Eh, peace, peace. Yay.
イエーイ。
Yay.
ゼータ、改めて3Dおめでとう！
Zeta, once again, congrats on your 3D!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
あ、ちなみに...
Ah, by the way...
何？
What?
えっと、これは... 1万円です。
Um, this is... 10,000 yen.
1万円？
10,000 yen?
100万円。
1,000,000 yen.
100万円！？ちょっとどっち？
1,000,000 yen!? Wait, which is it?
1万円で。
10,000 yen.
100万円。
1,000,000 yen.
いいえ、1万円で。
No, 10,000 yen.
いや、これ。
No, this.
ああ！
Ah!
おつサバです！
Otsu-saba-desu!
ああ、マイスター。ゼータミンが盗まれた。
Ah, my star. The Zeta Min was stolen.
My star... Senpai Zeta Min got stolen.
Okay, well... okay. (sigh) It's okay. I still have the key.
Aku masih punya kuncinya. Jadi, kita bakal pakai kunci ini untuk buka ruangan selanjutnya.
I still have the key. So, we will use this key
to open the next room.
I'm gonna use this key for the next room. Okay, let's go! Let's go!
I'm gonna use this key for the next room.
Okay, let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
わあ！うわあ！
Wow! Uwaa!
Finally! Now that we got the key, we unlocked this new room!
Finally! Now that we got the key,
we unlocked this new room!
Kok, tiba-tiba aku bisa masuk ke sini? Ini, bentar.
How did I suddenly enter here? This, wait.
Ah, ada instrumen segala macam. Wah. Wah.
Ah, there are all kinds of instruments. Wah. Wah.
It's also really, like, wide. 広いね。
It's also really, like, wide. It's wide, right?
Wah. What kind of place do you guys think this is? Hmm?
Band? No, no, no, no, no.
Emang boleh selucu ini? Ya boleh lah.
Is it okay to be this cute? Of course it is.
A music room? No, no, no, no.
Well, kind of. It's actually a Jazz Club! Wah.
Isn't that so cool?
Wait. Where did bass and drum? They... did they...
あれ？これチェロか。あ、ない。
Huh? Is this a cello? Ah, it's not here.
Ini drum. Hmm, drums, I see.
This is a drum. Hmm, drums, I see.
Drum roll. Oh, what's this? What's this?
Oh, electric guitar! (guitar sounds)
Oh. Oh, what about... what about this? It's a piano.
あれ？Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I see something over there.
Huh? Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
I see something over there.
あれ？それ猫じゃない？
Huh? Isn't that a cat?
Ah! It's Kochi! It's actually a cat! That's so cute!
(cute noises)
Ah, parah nih, enggak berespon kamu. Tidak sopan.
Ah, this is bad, you're not responding.
Disrespectful.
Hmm. Tidak sopan, tidak sopan. Aku enggak peduli.
Hmm. Disrespectful, disrespectful. I don't care.
Okay. Well. Look at this beautiful, beautiful piano. Hmm.
Okay. Well. Look at this beautiful,
beautiful piano. Hmm.
Should I... should I sit on it? Hmm, should I sit on it?
Should I... should I sit on it?
Hmm, should I sit on it?
What do you guys think? I'm just gonna take a seat.
What do you guys think?
I'm just gonna take a seat.
(sitting down grunt)
Ha ha ha ha. Bow down before me, peasants!
Bahasa kucing, enggak.
Cat language? No.
Cat cafe? Bukan. Ini Jazz Club, bukan cat cafe.
Cat cafe? No. This is a Jazz Club, not a cat cafe.
Yay! Okay. Um... maybe I should... maybe I should play a little bit?
Yay! Okay. Um... maybe I should...
maybe I should play a little bit?
Or am I? Or am I playing? Let's see.
(grunting) Okay. Okay okay.
Eh, kakiku enggak nyampe lantai. Thanks.
Eh, my feet don't reach the floor. Thanks.
Okay. Hmm.
Okay, you know what? Let's play!
Yay! Uhhh! Piano time, baby!
Apa main, apa dijokiin itu? Ha ha ha. Real kah?
Is she playing, or is it a bot? Haha. Is it real?
Yeah. Well, you know what? Since this is such a beautiful stage and all with all the instruments here and there...
Yeah. Well, you know what? Since this is such a
beautiful stage and all with all the instruments...
You know what? Might be a waste if we don't sing here, right?
You know what? Might be a waste if we don't
sing here, right?
Kayak udah jauh-jauh buka kunci, masuk Jazz Club, sia-sia dong kalau kita enggak nyanyi.
Since we unlocked and entered the Jazz Club,
it'd be a waste if we don't sing.
Iya enggak?
Right?
Should we sing?
Okay, you know what? Might as well. Let's sing!
揺らせ一秒 駆けだしたら Summer girls
Shake it for a second, once we start running, summer girls
夢への道はストレート
The road to dreams is straight
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと始まる Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is sure to begin
ゴールは Spotlight
The goal is the spotlight
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
I want you
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと始まる Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is sure to begin
みんな準備はいいですか？ Burning
Are you all ready? Burning
うなずいて 陽炎も Heat up
Nod along, even the heat haze is heating up
どうしよう 上昇 アガる空気 Let's go
What should I do? The air is rising and getting excited, let's go
さぁ太陽 燃えて最高
Now, sun, burn, it's the best
Mate 負けられない 興奮もハートも
Mate, I can't lose, my excitement and heart,
駆け引きは No no
no mind games
Gate 開いたなら 一瞬のドラマ
Gate, once it opens, it's a momentary drama
走れ 夏の方へ！
Run towards the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆けだしたら Summer girls
Shake it for a second, once we start running, summer girls
夢への道はストレート
The road to dreams is straight
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is sure to surge
ゴールは Spotlight
The goal is the spotlight
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
I want you
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is sure to surge
絶対 最上 掴みたい Feeling
Absolutely top-tier, the feeling I want to grasp
全身全霊 めぐるから Get hot
With all my heart and soul, it's circulating, so get hot
テンション 高揚 欲しいモノへ
Tension, exhilaration, towards what I want
今 Ride on time 待ってて It's show time
Now ride on time, wait for it, it's show time
Peak 迎えるとき 迂回はいらない
When reaching the peak, no detours are needed,
せめぎあい Oh oh
clashing with each other
Spark 汗とプライド ジレた運命
Spark, sweat and pride, an impatient fate
連れて 夏の方へ
Take me towards the summer
挑む世界は 魅惑の Sunlight floor
The world I challenge is the captivating sunlight floor
天井知らずのボルテージ
Voltage that knows no bounds
火照る季節を モノにして
Make the flushed season your own
Please, Gaze on Me! クラリさせたい Exciting time
Please, Gaze on Me! I want to make you dizzy in this exciting time
ゴールは Spotlight
The goal is the spotlight
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
I want you
Please, Gaze on Me! クラリさせたい Exciting time
Please, Gaze on Me! I want to make you dizzy in this exciting time
関係ない どんな私だって
It doesn't matter, no matter what kind of me
真夏 駆けだせたら Venus
In midsummer, if I can start running, Venus
アツくなれば 一歩で Change & Happy
If it gets hot, one step to change and happy
眩しすぎる今日を 踊るように手に入れよう
Let's seize this too-bright today as if dancing
さぁ Here we go!
Now, here we go!
ビートは止まらない
The beat won't stop
Keep 思うままに 身を預けて
Keep entrusting your body as you please
灼熱へ Go go
Into the scorching heat, go go
Warp 本能のリズム 打ち鳴らして
Warp, sounding out the rhythm of instinct
走れ 夏の方へ！
Run towards the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆けだしたら Summer girls
Shake it for a second, once we start running, summer girls
夢への道はストレート
The road to dreams is straight
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと始まる Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is sure to begin
ゴールは Spotlight
The goal is the spotlight
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
I want you
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと始まる Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! A fantastic time is sure to begin
うわー！ こんかざー！ ゼータ 3D おめでとう！
Wha-! Konkaza-! Zeta, congrats on your 3D!
ありがとう！ 来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you! Thanks for coming!
呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thanks for inviting me!
ありがとう、ありがとう。
Thank you, thank you.
あ、か、可愛いでござる、3D！
Ah, c-cute, in 3D-de gozaru!
えへへ。 先輩も可愛い！
Ehehe. You're cute too, Senpai!
うわー、やったー。 お揃い、ついに 3D。 一緒、一緒。 嬉しいでござる！
Whoa, yay! Matching 3Ds, finally. Together, together. I'm so happy-de gozaru!
私も嬉しい！
I'm happy too!
お洋服も可愛いけど、ねぇ、このステージもすごいおしゃれでござるな。
The clothes are cute, but hey, this stage is really stylish too-de gozaru.
ステージいいよね、広いよね。 めっちゃおしゃれ。
The stage is great, right? It's spacious. Very stylish.
ちなみに、あっちの方には何があるでござるか？
By the way, what's over that way-de gozaru?
じゃあ、案内するよ。
Then, I'll show you around.
案内してくれる？
You'll show me?
やった！ 行こう、行こう、行こう！
Yay! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
うわぁぁぁぁ！
Waaaaah!
おぉ、すごい！
Oh, amazing!
めっちゃ広い！
It's so spacious!
おっ、お洒落でござるな。
Oh, it's so stylish de-gozaru na.
うた、これゼタズクラブだから、ちょっとお洒落に。
Since this is Zeta's Club, it's a bit stylish.
ね、すごいお洒落！
Right? It's so stylish!
うおー！ステージがあっちでござるな。あとこっちから来たから、
Whoa! The stage is over there. And I came from this way,
お、すごい！かっこいいね、ゼタ。
Oh, amazing! It's cool, Zeta.
うん、めっちゃかっこいい。え、猫もあるよ。
Yeah, super cool. Oh, there's a cat too.
猫！見る？見る？
A cat! You want to see? You want to see?
猫見る！見る見る！
I want to see the cat! I want to see, I want to see!
猫だ！
It's a cat!
猫！
Cat!
触ってもいい？あ、いい？
Can I pet it? Oh, it's okay?
猫、猫！猫可愛い、猫可愛い！
Cat, cat! Cat's cute, cat's cute!
可愛い！猫可愛いでござるな、猫可愛い！
Cute! Cat is cute de-gozaru na, cat's cute!
あ、違う、猫じゃない。あ、違う違う。猫じゃない。ゼタ猫。
Ah, no, it's not a cat. Ah, no no. It's not a cat. Zeta cat.
あ、耳じゃない。あ、耳じゃない。そうかそうか。
Ah, it's not ears. Ah, it's not ears. I see, I see.
猫可愛い、猫可愛い、ゼタも可愛い！
Cat's cute, cat's cute, Zeta's also cute!
可愛いね。
You're cute.
え、あとあと、なんか... 実はね、プレゼントがあって。プレゼントあげます！
Um, also, also, like... actually, I have a present. I'll give you a present!
あ、やった！プレゼント！
Oh, yay! A present!
これ。ゼタミン。
This. Zetamin.
ZETAMIN
え、すごい！ゼタミン！これ飲んだら...
Eh, amazing! Zetamin! If I drink this...
頭が賢くなる。強、強、強い。
Your head becomes smart. Strong, strong, strong.
強、強い！そうそう、もっと強くなる。
Strong, strong! Yeah, yeah, you'll become even stronger.
すごい！パワーアップアイテム！
Amazing! A power-up item!
いや、パワーアップアイテム！
Indeed, a power-up item!
スペシャルアイテム！
A special item!
やったー！サンキュー、ゼタ。大事にします。ありがとう、大事にしよう。
Yay! Thank you, Zeta. I'll treasure it. Thank you, I'll treasure it.
じゃあ、どうぞ座ってください。
Well then, please take a seat.
ありがとう。じゃあちょっとね、座ろうかな。
Thank you. Then I'll, you know, sit down.
喋ろう。
Let's talk.
うわー、すごい。椅子もとてもいい感じでござるな。
Whoa, amazing. This chair is also very nice de-gozaru na.
いいよね。ふわふわ。
It's nice, right? Fluffy.
ね、改めて今日は呼んでくれてありがとうでござる。
Hey, thanks again for inviting me today de-gozaru.
いいえ、こちらこそありがとう。
No, thank you as well.
なんで今日はさ、風真のこと呼んでくれたの？
So, why did you invite Kazama today?
え、好きだから。
Uh, because I like you.
えー！そんな、そんなストレートに... 嬉しい！
Ehh! So... so straightforwardly... I'm happy!
え、コラボとかもさ、なんか...
Um, and we've collaborated, like...
あ、確かに、何回か。っていうか、いっぱいくらいかな？2、3回して... 結構何回かしてる。
Ah, certainly, a few times. Or rather, quite a lot? 2 or 3 times... quite a few times.
そうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
なんか、まあ、とにかく好きになっちゃって。
Like, well, anyway, I've come to like you.
え、そんな... 嬉しいでござる。
Ehh... I'm so happy de-gozaru.
それで呼んでくれたんだ、今日。
That's why you invited me today.
そうそうそう。
Yes, yes, yes.
ありがとう。で、今日ね、一緒に歌わせていただいた曲が「Gaze on Me」っていう曲で、
Thank you. And today, the song we sang together was "Gaze on Me",
その、風真も、あの、すいせい先輩の3Dライブで知ったんだけど、ゼタもすいせい先輩の3Dライブで知ったんだっけ？
And, Kazama also, um, learned it from Suisei-senpai's 3D live, but did Zeta also learn it from Suisei-senpai's 3D live?
そうそう。見たことあって。
Yeah, yeah. I've seen it.
そうってことでね、この曲一緒に歌わせていただけて... いや、楽しかった。一緒に歌えて楽しかったでござる。
Right, so, being able to sing this song together... man, it was fun. It was fun singing together de-gozaru.
いや、曲はね、「Gaze on Me」。曲が本当に好きなので、
No, the song, "Gaze on Me". I really love the song, so...
なんか、お二人で一緒に踊りたい、歌いたい。し、だから選んだ。
Like, I wanted the two of us to dance and sing together. That's why I chose it.
はー！呼んでくれたんだ、風真のことを。風真のこと選んでくれたってこと。
Haa! So you invited me. You chose Kazama.
うん。
Yeah.
嬉しい！ありがとう！でも本当に一緒に歌って踊れて、すごく楽しかったでござる。
I'm happy! Thank you! But really, being able to sing and dance together was so much fun de-gozaru.
ね、風真これからもゼタと一緒に歌ったり踊ったり、せっかく3Dになったから、すごくやりたいなって思うんだけど、ゼタはどうですか？
Hey, from now on Kazama wants to sing and dance with Zeta, especially since we're finally 3D. What do you think, Zeta?
え、一緒にダンスしたい！一緒に歌いたい！
Eh, I want to dance together! I want to sing together!
本当に？やった！それじゃあこれからもいっぱいいっしょに歌って、踊って、やろうね！
Really? Yay! Then from now on, let's sing and dance together a lot!
またやろうね！他の曲もやりましょう！
Let's do it again! Let's do other songs too!
や、やりましょう。はい、ね。今日は本当に改めて呼んでくれてありがとう、そして、3Dおめでとうでござる！
Ye... yes, let's. Yes. Truly, thank you again for inviting me today, and congratulations on your 3D de-gozaru!
わー、ありがとう！
Wow, thank you!
風真そろそろ行かなきゃいけないけど...
Kazama has to go soon, but...
どこ行くの？行くの？行っちゃうの？
Where are you going? You're going? You're leaving?
大丈夫、ずっと近くでゼタのこのあとのステージも見てるでござるから。だからね、応援してる、ゼタ。頑張って。
It's okay, I'll be watching Zeta's stage from close by after this. So, I'm cheering for you, Zeta. Good luck.
行っちゃだめ！行っちゃだめ！行っちゃだめ！行っちゃだめ！行っちゃだめ！寂しいの、寂しい。
Don't go! Don't go! Don't go! Don't go! Don't go! I'll be lonely, lonely.
え、わかった、風真特等席で見てる。ずっと見てるから、このあとも頑張って。ずっと見てるよ。じゃあ頑張る、頑張る！よし、じゃあ大好き！もう頑張ろうね、風真と心は一つだよ。
Eh, okay, Kazama will watch from the VIP seat. I'll be watching the whole time, so do your best after this. I'm always watching. Then I'll do my best, my best! Okay, then I love you! Let's do our best, our hearts are as one.
うん、ずっと一緒。
Yeah, together forever.
うん。
Yeah.
おす。
Push.
ハート・トゥ・ハート。
Heart-to-heart.
OK, OK.
じゃ、頑張ってね。
Well, good luck.
応援してます。
I'm rooting for you.
またね。
See ya.
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
That was Nene-senpai!
She was so cute.
But don't go anywhere...
...because we're going to the next song!
次の曲...
The next song...
...行こう！
...let's go!
ハレ晴レユカイ
ゼータ ＆ ムメイ
Hare Hare Yukai
Zeta & Mumei
謎なぞみたいに地球儀を解き明かしたら
If we solve the globe like a riddle
みんなでどこまでも行けるね
We can go anywhere together
ワクワクしたいと願いながら過ごしてたよ
I spent my days wishing for excitement
叶えてくれたのは誰なの？
Who was it that made it come true?
時間の果てまで
To the end of time
Boooon!!
ワープでループなこの思いは
These feelings that warp and loop
何もかも巻き込んだ想像で遊ぼう
Let's play with an imagination that involves everything
ある晴れた日のこと
One sunny day
魔法以上のユカイが
A fun that's more than magic
限りなく降りそそぐ
Will fall down endlessly
不可能じゃないわ
It's not impossible
明日また会う時
When we meet again tomorrow
笑いながらハミング
Humming while laughing
嬉しさを集めよう
Let's collect happiness
簡単なんだよ、こんなの
Something like this is simple
追いかけてね
Please chase after me
捕まえてみて
Try and catch me
大きな夢＆夢
A big dream & dream
始まるでしょ？
It's starting, right?
いろいろ予想ができそうでできない未来
A future that seems predictable but isn't
それでもひとつだけわかるよ
But even so, there's one thing I know
キラキラ光って熱い雲の上を飾る
Sparkling and decorating the top of hot clouds
星たちが希望をくれると
The stars give us hope
時間に乗ろうよ
Let's ride on time
Byuuun!!
チープでクールな年頃だもん
We're in that cheap and cool age
寂しがっちゃ恥ずかしいよなんてね
It's embarrassing to be lonely, or so I say
言わせて
Let me say it
手と手をつないだら
If we hold hands
向かう所敵なしでしょ
We'll be invincible wherever we go
輝いた瞳には
In those shining eyes
不可能がないの
There is no impossibility
上だけ見ていると
If you only look up
涙も乾いちゃう
Even tears will dry
変わりたい心から
Because I want to change from my heart
強く思うほど伝わる
The stronger I think it, the more it's felt
走り出すよ
I'll start running
後ろの人も
You there in the back too
おいでよドキドキ
Come here, isn't your heart...
するでしょ？
...beating fast?
Boooon!!
ワープでループなこの思いは
These feelings that warp and loop
何もかも巻き込んだ想像で遊ぼう
Let's play with an imagination that involves everything
ある晴れた日のこと
One sunny day
魔法以上のユカイが
A fun that's more than magic
限りなく降りそそぐ
Will fall down endlessly
不可能じゃないわ
It's not impossible
明日また会う時
When we meet again tomorrow
笑いながらハミング
Humming while laughing
嬉しさを集めよう
Let's collect happiness
簡単なんだよ、こんなの
Something like this is simple
追いかけてね
Please chase after me
捕まえてみて
Try and catch me
大きな夢＆夢
A big dream & dream
始まるでしょ？
It's starting, right?
Yay, I'm so glad I moved with Mumei!
ムメイ可愛かったよね。
Mumei was so cute.
It was so much fun singing...
...singing and dancing with her.
It was so much fun, she was so cute.
素晴らしいパフォーマンス、ゼータさん。
Splendid performance, Zeta-san.
はっ？
Huh?
Wait, whose voice is that?
Is that... YAGOO?
こんにちは。
Hello.
YAGOO! YAGOO!
Wait, why are you here?
I'm a VIP guest.
はっ？
Huh?
Now then.
Actually, I saw that the door to the jazz club was open...
...so I just came in.
I have been watching you since the beginning.
Oh, oh. Okay. Uh...
Okay!
Well, well. You know what? Since you're already here anyway...
...do you want to try singing like the song earlier...
...together?
Oh, yeah, sure. Akujokuamao.
Akujokuamao! Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah. Okay, wow!
Okay, look guys, we can finally hear Yagoo sing! Yay!
Now?
Yeah, now! If not now, then when?
Ya-u-ta-i-ya, Ze-ta-i-ya...
Ah...
He's going to sing... Ah!
Lha, malah buka baju!
Wait, he's taking off his shirt!
Lha!
Wait!
What? He took off...
baju?!
...his shirt?!
No! No!
No, YAGOO! YAGOO!
Basso, why did you take YAGOO away?
That's my VIP guest!
Where are you going?
YAGOO行っちゃったよ...
YAGOO went away...
YAGOO...
YAGOO left. Oh no.
But it's okay. It's okay, it's okay because...
...we can just call more guests, right?
We can call more guests.
Who cares if YAGOO is gone?
じゃ、ゲスト呼んでみようか。
Well, let's try calling another guest.
もしもし、もしもし、もしもし。
Hello? Hello? Hello?
みんな！
Everyone!
こより！リス！オリー！アメ！
Koyori! Risu! Ollie! Ame!
Yay! Waaa!
かわいい！
So cute!
Wow! Wow! Hi! Thank you so much for coming!
Hi, thank you so much for coming, Koyori, Risu, Ollie, Ame!
Thank you for coming!
Alright, so the reason why I called you guys is...
...to do the regular old screenshot time.
However...
Ooooh!
...we were gonna do something different. So, how about the first person...
...go with like an easy pose, okay?
Jadi orang pertama posenya easy. Level 1 pose.
So the first person's pose is easy. Level 1 pose.
And then, next person...
...the pose gets harder each time, okay? Level 2, level 3, level 4, okay?
Okay! Okay!
Okay? Okay?
So, I trust you guys to give me poses.
写真タイムだよ、みんな。写真撮って。
Screenshot time, everyone! Take a picture!
Okay, so... from the easiest one...
...who's gonna give me the easiest pose?
リス先輩！リス先輩！
Risu-senpai! Risu-senpai!
Zeta-ko! Hi, hi!
Hi, Risu-senpai! Come on, what pose? What pose?
Oke, karena aku, aku baik, aku baik.
Okay, because I'm, I'm kind, I'm kind.
Yeah, yeah, baik, baik.
Yeah, yeah, kind, kind.
Jadi sebagai secret agent yang baik nih...
So as a good secret agent...
...kamu harus bisa kamuflase.
...you have to be able to camouflage.
Kamuflase? Okay, camouflage, okay, okay.
Camouflage? Okay, camouflage, okay, okay.
Jadi aku mau kamu kamuflase...
So I want you to camouflage...
...jadi T-Rex.
...as a T-Rex.
T-Rex!
T-Rex? Like dinosaur T-Rex?
Iya, T-Rex yang tangannya kecil itu lho.
Yeah, the T-Rex with the small arms.
Okay, fine, fine, fine. Okay, okay. Gotta do it quickly.
Gini?
Like this?
Kepalanya ke belakang ya?
Head back, okay?
Ha?
Huh?
Iya, kepalanya ke belakang.
Yeah, head back.
Udah, ini udah ke belakang!
Already, it's already back!
Gini?
Like this?
Gini? Udah? Udah?
Like this? Enough? Enough?
Ini ngerjain, ini ngerjain kouhai namanya.
This is picking on, this is picking on your kouhai.
This is bullying-kouhai territory.
This is bullying-kouhai territory. I'm good, I'm good.
I'm good, good. Okay, that was easy.
優しいね、みんな。優しいね。
See? I'm kind, right?
I mean, that was pretty easy. That was pretty easy.
Something like that... too easy, too easy.
Thank you, リス先輩！
Thank you, Risu-senpai!
How was that T-Rex enough for you?
That is so cute! Very cute T-Rex!
Okay, thank you. Well... oh.
I don't know who... um...
Who should we go? こより or オリー先輩、アメ？
Who should we go? Koyori or Ollie-senpai, Ame?
Okay, what about... okay, what about...
こより！
Koyori!
Yay! Zeta-chan! こよみー！
Yay! Zeta-chan! Koyomi!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming!
こちらこそ、thank you very much!
Same here, thank you very much!
Thank you very much! Hi! So good.
何か、ポーズちょうだい！
Please give me a pose!
Okay! Hi!
I want you to do the pose I promised you before...
...in the totsumachi!
Whoa, okay! Great English! Okay, okay.
In the totsumachi! In the totsumachi.
凸待ちで約束したやつです。
It's the one I promised in the totsumachi.
あ、おぼえてる？
Ah, do you remember?
ねこのやつ？
The cat one?
そう！腰振りねこダンス！
Yeah! The hip-sway cat dance!
Neko swaying cat dance! Okay!
Neko... いきいき上がり... OK, Neko Dance!
Neko... feeling lively... OK, cat dance!
Okay, Neko Dance okay! Okay, Neko Dance okay!
Okay, cat dance okay! Okay, cat dance okay!
腰振りねこダンス！ねこダンス！
Hip-sway cat dance! Cat dance!
ねこダンス！可愛い可愛い！
Cat dance! So cute, so cute!
ねこダンス！にゃー、にゃー！
Cat dance! Nya, nya!
にゃー、にゃー、にゃー！
Nya, nya, nya!
もっと！もっとパワー！
More! More power!
Power up! More power! Okay, we need doping.
Maybe we need... something to increase my...
Zetamin! Power up! Okay, okay!
わあ！ねこダンス！にゃー、にゃー！
Whoa! Cat dance! Nya, nya!
にゃー、にゃー！あー、疲れた。
Nya, nya! Ah, I'm tired.
可愛い！ありがとう！よく頑張りました！
So cute! Thank you! You did a great job!
ありがとう、こよりん！Thank you!
Thank you, Koyori! Thank you!
じゃ、次の... request...
Now, the next... request...
Ayo, siapa lagi? Okay, what about Ollie-senpai?
Come on, who else? Okay, what about Ollie-senpai?
Me! Me! Me! Yay! I choose you!
Ayo, bisa apa? Yang paling susah.
Come on, what can you do? Give me the hardest one.
Okay, but first of all, I heard you already had a gun also.
Oh, I do have a gun, yeah. Really? I want to see it!
Tada! Whoa, that's so cool!
The pose ready in my head.
The pose is ready in my head.
Aku pengen kamu jongkok. Okay, jongkok.
I want you to squat. Okay, squat.
Jongkok gini?
Squat like this?
Yeah, terus salah satu kaki kamu diselonjorin.
Yeah, then stretch out one of your legs.
Gini? Oh, bahaya! Ya, kayak gitu.
Like this? Oh, dangerous! Yeah, like that.
Terus abis itu, kamu kayak tembak ke bagian atas kirinya kamu gitu.
And then, you shoot towards your upper left like that.
Pa-pa-pa-pa! Whoa, so cool!
Like a secret agent! Yeah!
Okay, this is a little bit tough. Maybe we go the other way.
Pa-pa-pa-pa! Whoa! Nggak boleh, nggak boleh madep kalian.
Pa-pa-pa-pa! Whoa! Can't, can't face you guys.
Hahaha, keren banget! Okay, thank you Ollie-senpai!
Hahaha, so cool! Okay, thank you Ollie-senpai!
Okay, next person. Ame! Thank you for coming, Ame!
Oh my God, Ame! Ame! Oh no, Ame!
Okay, Ame, give me your the most difficult pose!
Okay, Ame, give me your most difficult pose!
The hardest one? Okay, okay.
You know, as a secret agent, it must be pretty tough to...
...balance properly, to find inner peace in the middle of stress.
Inner peace... okay, okay.
So, yeah, I need you to balance on one foot... wait, wait.
Do you have anything to put on your head maybe that you could balance on?
I mean, I don't have anything, I only have... I have like Baso or...
I have Zetamin, I guess! Oh, that'll work!
If I drop it, it'll... whoa! It's so heavy!
So heavy! So cute!
Okay, let's see if you can balance Zetamin on your head and stand on one foot.
Okay, on my head, and then stay on one foot.
Yeah... like this? Wait... yeah, yeah!
Wait, this is too easy! It's too easy for you!
How is this easy? This is not easy at all! I'm falling!
No, no, we gotta up the difficulty. No hands! No hands!
No hands? Okay, wait... ah-t-t-t-t!
Whoa! Okay, okay! Can you hold it for three seconds? Does three seconds count?
Okay... whoa! Okay there!
Okay, I hope that counts! That counts! Wait, wait, I have a question.
Are we going to get our Zetamin in the mail for our participation?
Oh, yeah! Of course! I'll deliver the Zetamin personally to you.
Yay! Thank you everyone for coming! 来てくれてありがとう！
Yay! Thank you everyone for coming! Thank you for coming!
That was so much fun! Thank you for the performance! おめでとう！
That was so much fun! Thank you for the performance! Congratulations!
Thank you! Thank you, everyone! Bye-bye-nyan!
Bye-bye! Thank you!
Whoo! Okay, it's not over yet until I say it's over.
Belum selesai karena aku mau menunjukkan sesuatu, yaitu...
It's not over yet because I want to show you something, which is...
...apa tuh? New merch! New goods! Let's take a look!
...what is it? New merch! New goods! Let's take a look!
holoh3ro Card Case - Vestia Zeta
Oh, so cool!
It's like a business card...
...there's like the case, and then inside is a business card.
Jadi ada case, terus di dalamnya ada business card.
So there's a case, and inside there's a business card.
カード欲しいでしょ？欲しいんでしょ？
You want the card, right? You want it, don't you?
I mean, who, you know, as a secret agent, I'm a professional secret agent...
...so I have to have a business card.
Well, if you want to be nge-penge-peng amat, aku kasih lihat versi real, versi 3D!
Well, if you're really curious, I'll show you the real version, the 3D version!
Tada!
It's the business card!
Look, isn't it so cute?
Mine is gray. Punya aku abu-abu gitu.
Mine is gray. Mine is kind of gray.
Zetaのはグレーになっちゃってるけど、可愛いでしょ？
Zeta's turned out gray, but isn't it cute?
Isn't it so cute? Would you like to buy this?
Aku mau gas, aku juga mau, nice!
I'm in, I want one too, nice!
So cool, strategi marketing nice!
So cool, nice marketing strategy!
Ayo dibeli!
Come on, buy it!
Versi real, iya versi real.
Real version, yeah, real version.
Yay!
Okay, anyway... It's gonna be on sale after the 3D collab stream...
...on the 28th of October. So, yeah.
Nanti bakal ada on-sale pas holoh3ro 3D collab. Okay?
It will be on sale during the holoh3ro 3D collab. Okay?
Gimana? Kakkoi? Skip ad? Gak boleh skip ad!
How is it? Cool? Skip ad? You can't skip the ad!
Aku mau sepuluh!
I want ten!
Mau dong! Kayang? Tadi udah kayang.
I want one! Bridge pose? I already did a bridge earlier.
Impressive, very nice. Okay, seems like everyone wants it.
Okay, wow. Do you guys want me to continue my 3D more, or do you want this business card more?
I wonder which you like more.
Skip? You can't skip!
I have an obligation, okay, to show this.
Okay, I think it's time to sing my last song.
Tiba-tiba emo, hmm...
Suddenly getting emo, hmm...
You guys want to know what the song is? You guys probably already know what the song is.
Kalian udah tahu nggak sih kira-kira gaya lagunya tuh apa?
Do you guys already know what kind of song it is?
Ayo apa? Apa? Apa?
Come on, what is it? What? What?
Lagu apa tuh? Lagu apa?
What song is that? What song?
Hello? Lagu apa? Let me hear you.
Hello? What song? Let me hear you.
Encore? No, no, no.
Yes! Original song! Yes! Somebody said original song!
Yes! I'm going to be singing my original song, original song!
Wow, tanjoubi? Original song!
Wow, birthday? Original song!
The title is... "You're Mine".
As the city lights come alive / Shadows of the night
Help me spin my web
Got my target there in my sight
He can run and hide but he can't be saved
Goin' in as I make my move smooth as that jazzy groove
While the music's playin'
Lethal with a drink in my hand
I've been working a plan and it's goin' good
Cheers to all your secrets, your desires
全てを手に入れるまで I won't stop
Until I have it all, I won't stop
Don't you hide from me
I can see through your eyes
秘密だって
Even if it's a secret
Locked away でも隠しきれない
Locked away, but you can't hide it all
最強な Secret agent 罠をかければ...
The strongest secret agent, if I set a trap...
You're mine
I can see through your eyes どこにいても
I can see through your eyes, no matter where you are
In the dark でも逃げきれない
In the dark, you still can't escape
最強な Super power 今すぐ捕まえる
A strongest superpower, catching you right now
捕まえる
Catching you
Got him all caught up in my web
Every word he's said, ready for replay
Then I slipped and he knew my hand
Took off and he ran, thought he could escape
Cheers to all your secrets, your desires
今さら気付いても too late 'cause I won't stop
It's too late even if you notice now, 'cause I won't stop
Don't you hide from me
Catch and release? Do you think? そんなヘマはしない 最後に仕留めるのが
Catch and release? What do you think? I won't make such a mistake, I'll finish you off at the end
最後に仕留めるのが my style
Finishing you off is my style
Let you swim for now but
You're すでに mine
You're already mine
Just reel in the line
No matter how far you may run to...
I can see through your eyes
どこにいても
Wherever you are
In the dark
でも逃げ切れない
You still can't escape
最強な super power
With the strongest super power
でつかまえる
I'll catch you
I can see through your eyes
秘密だって
Even secrets
Locked away
でも隠しきれない
Can't be hidden away
最強な secret agent
The strongest secret agent
罠をかければ...
Once I set the trap...
You're mine
I can see through your eyes
どこにいても
Wherever you are
In the dark
でも逃げ切れない
You still can't escape
最強な super power
With the strongest super power
でつかまえる
I'll catch you
Baby you're mine
Run but you can't hide
狙ったらもう離さない
Once I aim, I won't let go
Baby you're mine
Always one step behind
I'll take my time
Cause baby you're mine
Ah, that was, that was my first original song,
"You're Mine!"
I'm glad you guys enjoyed the song.
Did you like the song?
The song is about a secr—
A secret agent who's trying to find her target and catch her target.
That's why it's called "You're Mine". Yeah.
I'm tired.
Well, if you want to see the song jacket, look over here!
Jaja~n!
Ta-da!
Yay! Isn't it so cute?
可愛いでしょう？
Cute, right?
Yeah, it's gonna be released tonight actually. Tonight!
So be sure to stream "You're Mine", okay?
Watch the MV.
Okay, so I guess that concludes today's mission.
I guess...
Lah, ada penyusup!
Wait, an intruder!
Lah, siapa?
Wait, who?
Lah, kok bisa masuk sini?
Wait, how can they enter here?
Lah, Vestia Zeta?
Wait, Vestia Zeta?
Loh, kok kamu baru tahu sekarang?
Wait, you're only finding out now?
Ah, I'm getting found out!
Oh no!
Dahlah.
I'm done.
Woi, kamu! Siapa namanya?
Hey, you! What's your name?
Berhenti di situ! Jangan gerak!
Stop right there! Don't move!
Kita ke lokasi sekarang.
We're heading to the location now.
Ah, aku... aku... aku bukan penyusup!
Ah, I... I... I'm not an intruder!
Aku bukan penyusup!
I'm not an intruder!
Halo? Halo? Halo? Halo?
Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello?
Ya gimana? Ya udah aku harus lari sekarang.
So what? Alright, I have to run now.
I have to, I have to escape now.
I can't be caught here.
Well, see you! See you! Bye, bye!
Zecretary, you're the reason why I smile and look forward to tomorrow! Thank you for everything! Zeta